Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Contact Sheets, Series 2
  - Contact sheet 2004, 1993 Aug. 19; 2004 (Item 40)
    New York City; street scenes; lighting Jahrzeit candle
  - Contact sheet 2005, 1993 Aug. 15; 2005 (Item 40)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christian Church window; homeless
  - Contact sheet 2006, 1993 Aug. 21; 2006 (Item 40)
    New York City; Yankee Springs; George Condo with Allen Ginsberg's portrait
  - Contact sheet 2007, 1993 Aug. 22; 2007 (Item 40)
    "Berkeley, CA; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2008, 1993 Aug. 24; 2008 (Item 40)
    "Yankee Springs, MI; Yankee Springs Retreat"
  - Contact sheet 2009, 1993 Aug. 25; 2009 (Item 40)
    "Yankee Springs, MI; San Francisco, CA"
  - Contact sheet 2010, 1993 Aug. 26; 2010 (Item 40)
    "Yankee Springs, MI; San Francisco, CA; Yankee Springs Retreat"
  - Contact sheet 2011, 1993 Aug. 27; 2011 (Item 40)
  - Contact sheet 2012, 1993 Aug. 29; 2012 (Item 40)
  - Contact sheet 2013, 1993 Aug. 30; 2013 (Item 40)
    New York City; street vendors; street scenes; St. Ann's rectory; garbage truck
  - Contact sheet 2014, 1993 Aug. 31; 2014 (Item 40)
    Luke Elliott
  - Contact sheet 2015, 1993 Aug. 31; 2015 (Item 40)
  - Contact sheet 2016, 1993 Sept. 4; 2016 (Item 40)
    "Woodstock, NY"
  - Contact sheet 2017, 1993 Sept. 5; 2017 (Item 40)
    "Woodstock, NY; Robert Frank on the Bowery"
  - Contact sheet 2018, 1993 Sept. 8; 2018 (Item 40)
    "Vienna, Austria"
  - Contact sheet 2019, 1993 Sept. 8; 2019 (Item 40)
  - Contact sheet 2020, 1993 Sept. 11; 2020 (Item 40)
  - Contact sheet 2021, 1993 Sept. 11; 2021 (Item 41)
    "Vienna, Austria; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2022, 1993 Sept. 12; 2022 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2023, 1993 Sept. 13; 2023 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2024, 1993 Sept. 16; 2024 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2025, 1993 Sept. 18; 2025 (Item 41)
    "Vienna, Austria; museum display of Venus"
  - Contact sheet 2026, 1993 Sept. 19; 2026 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2027, 1993 Sept. 19; 2027 (Item 41)
    "Vienna, Austria; New York City; Joseph Logan and Peter Hale dressed for Wigstock"
  - Contact sheet 2029, 1993 Sept. 25; 2029 (Item 41)
    "Vienna, Austria; Budapest, Hungary"
  - Contact sheet 2030, 1993 Sept. 27; 2030 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2031.1, 1993 Sept. 28; 2031.1 (Item 41)
    "Budapest, Hungary; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2031.2, 1993 Sept. 28; 2031.2 (Item 41)
    "COLOR: Budapest, Hungary; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2031.3, 1993 Sept. 28; 2031.3 (Item 41)
    Istvan Eorsi
  - Contact sheet 2032, 1993 Sept. 29; 2032 (Item 41)
    "Budapest, Hungary; Belgrade, Yugoslavia?; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2033, 1993 Oct. 6; 2033 (Item 41)
    "Lodes, Poland; Lodes Ghetto; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2034, 1993 Oct. 11; 2034 (Item 41)
    "Warsaw, Poland; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2035, 1993 Oct. 15; 2035 (Item 41)
    "Paris, France; Shakespeare and Co. bookstore"
  - Contact sheet 2036, 1993 Oct. 16; 2036 (Item 41)
    "London, England; Dublin, Ireland; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2037, 1993 Oct. 18; 2037 (Item 41)
    "Dublin, Ireland; Yeats' grave"
  - Contact sheet 2038, 1993 Oct. 20; 2038 (Item 41)
    "Dublin, Ireland; new Book of Kells"
  - Contact sheet 2039, 1993 Oct. 22; 2039 (Item 41)
    Morocco; Paul Bowles' house?; city scenes
  - Contact sheet 2040, 1993 Oct. 28; 2040 (Item 41)
    "Dublin, Ireland"
  - Contact sheet 2041, 1993 Nov. 4; 2041 (Item 41)
    "Oslo, Norway"
  - Contact sheet 2042, 1993 Nov. 5; 2042 (Item 41)
    "Munich, Germany; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2043, 1993 Nov. 10; 2043 (Item 41)
    "Paris, France; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Jean Jacques Lebel award; marionettes"
  - Contact sheet 2044, 1993 Nov. 12; 2044 (Item 41)
    "Lyons, Paris, France; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Ginsberg on television; Christian Bourgois"
  - Contact sheet 2045, 1993 Nov. 13; 2045 (Item 41)
    "Madrid, Barcelona, Spain; Miro tapestry; Hotel Sulcia"
  - Contact sheet 2046, 1993 Nov. 14; 2046 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2047, 1993 Nov. 14; 2047 (Item 41)
    "Paris, France; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2048, 1993 Nov. 15; 2048 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2049, 1993 Nov. 18; 2049 (Item 41)
  - Contact sheet 2050, 1993 Dec. 5; 2050 (Item 41)
    "Prague, Czechoslavakia"
  - Contact sheet 2051, 1993 Dec. 5; 2051 (Item 42)
    "Prague, Czechoslavakia; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; cathedral; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2052, 1993 Dec. 8; 2052 (Item 42)
    "Barcelona, Spain; Prague, Czechoslovakia; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2053, 1993 Dec. 10; 2053 (Item 42)
    "Barcelona, Spain; Prague, Czechoslovakia; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes; Gaudi cathedral"
  - Contact sheet 2054, 1993 Dec. 11; 2054 (Item 42)
    "Barcelona, Spain"
  - Contact sheet 2055, 1993 Dec. 18; 2055 (Item 42)
    "Athens, Greece; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2056, 1993 Dec. 22; 2056 (Item 42)
    "Athens, Greece; Greek soldiers at the Acropolis; shop window; Parthenon"
  - Contact sheet 2057, 1993 Dec. 23; 2057 (Item 42)
    "Tangiers, Morocco; Villa Muniera"
  - Contact sheet 2058, 1993 Dec. 24; 2058 (Item 42)
    "Tangiers, Morocco"
  - Contact sheet 2059, 1993 Dec. 24; 2059 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2060, 1993 Dec. 25; 2060 (Item 42)
    "Tangiers, Morocco; Christmas noon, Villa Muniera"
    Bowles, Paul, 1910–1999
  - Contact sheet 2061, 1993 Dec. 25; 2061 (Item 42)
    "Tangiers, Morocco; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2062, 1993? Jan. 11; 2062 (Item 42)
    "Ann Arbor, MI; retreat; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2063, 1994 Jan. 13; 2063 (Item 42)
    "COLOR:San Francisco, CA; New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ; Aunt Honey Litzky's house; Edith Ginsberg in Elmwood Park; kitchen window views; from hotel window Stutter St. San Francisco; Kronos Quartet, San Francisco; Philip Whalen in Chinese restaurant"
  - Contact sheet 2064.1, 1994 Jan. 18; 2064.1 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2064.2, 1994 Jan. 24; 2064.2 (Item 42)
    New York City; Mary Help of Christians Church wedding; Kronos Quartet
  - Contact sheet 2065, 1994 Feb. 8; 2065 (Item 42)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Allen Ginsberg at Paterson Falls; skyline"
  - Contact sheet 2066, 1994 Feb. 6; 2066 (Item 42)
    "Paterson, NJ; Edith Ginsberg's birthday"
  - Contact sheet 2067, 1994 Feb. 6; 2067 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2068, 1994 Feb. 12; 2068 (Item 42)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Shambhala day
  - Contact sheet 2069, 1994 Feb. 13; 2069 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2070, 1994 Feb. 13; 2070 (Item 42)
    "New York City; Paris, France; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2071, 1994 Feb. 26; 2071 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2072, 1994 Mar. 3; 2072 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2073, 1994 Mar. 18; 2073 (Item 42)
    "Montreal, Canada; Berlin, Germany; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 2074, 1994 Mar. 19; 2074 (Item 42)
    New York City; homeless in doorway
  - Contact sheet 2075, 1994 Mar. 29; 2075 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2076, 1994 Apr. 1; 2076 (Item 42)
    New York City; first spring day; Vajracharia; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 2077, 1994 Apr. 14; 2077 (Item 42)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes; road repair crew; Milo Printing window; 12th and Avenue A
  - Contact sheet 2078, 1994 Apr. 14; 2078 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2079, 1994 Apr. 14; 2079 (Item 42)
    New York City; street person with dogs
  - Contact sheet 2080, 1994 Apr. 23; 2080 (Item 42)
  - Contact sheet 2081, 1994 Apr. 23; 2081 (Item 43)
    New York City; [date uncertain]; Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 2082, 1994 Apr. 8; 2082 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2083, 1994 Apr. 23; 2083 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2084, 1994 Apr. 26; 2084 (Item 43)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Tompkins Square Park
  - Contact sheet 2085, 1994 Apr. 29; 2085 (Item 43)
    "New York City; Portland, ME; homeless; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2086, 1994 May 4; 2086 (Item 43)
    "New York City; Portland, ME; Mary Help of Christians Church window; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2087, 1994 May 9; 2087 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2088, 1994 May 13; 2088 (Item 43)
    "New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ"
  - Contact sheet 2089.1, 1994 May 14; 2089.1 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2089.2, 1994 May 14; 2089.2 (Item 43)
    COLOR: New York City; [May 14? 1994] Anthony Vitale at Mee restaurant
  - Contact sheet 2090, 1994 May 18; 2090 (Item 43)
    New York City; Kerouac Festival at NYU; kitchen window views; Peter Stuyvesant statue; Hassidic men at Beth Israel hospital
    NYU
  - Contact sheet 2091, 1994 May 19; 2091 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2092, 1994 May 20; 2092 (Item 43)
    New York City; NYU Beat Conference
  - Contact sheet 2093, 1994 May 20; 2093 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2095, 1994 May 21; 2095 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2096, 1994 May 22; 2096 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2097, 1994 May 22; 2097 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2098, 1994 May 24; 2098 (Item 43)
    New York City; NYU Beat Conference; NYU; kitchen window views; skyline at night
  - Contact sheet 2099, 1994 June 4; 2099 (Item 43)
    "New York City; Plainview, NY; NYU Beat Conference; homeless street people; skyline at night"
  - Contact sheet 2100, 1994 June 4; 2100 (Item 43)
    New York City; NYU Beat Conference; bookstore display window; American Academy
  - Contact sheet 2101, 1994 June 4; 2101 (Item 43)
    "New York City; Hastings-on-Hudson, NY; San Francisco, CA"
  - Contact sheet 2102, 1994 June 10; 2102 (Item 43)
    "Chicago, IL; New York City; Boston, MA; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2103, 1994 June 12; 2103 (Item 43)
    "Seattle, WA; Chicago, IL"
  - Contact sheet 2104, 1994 June 21; 2104 (Item 43)
    "Seattle, WA; Chicago, IL; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; skyscrapers, city views; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2105, 1994 June 27; 2105 (Item 43)
    "Lawrence, KS; New York City; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2106, 1994 June 28; 2106 (Item 43)
    "Lawrence, KS; Seattle, WA; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2107, 1994 June 29; 2107 (Item 43)
    "Lawrence, KS; Seattle, WA"
  - Contact sheet 2108, 1994 June 30; 2108 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2109, 1994 July 8; 2109 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2110, 1994 July 10; 2110 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2111, 1994 July 12; 2111 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2112, 1994 July 16; 2112 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2113, 1994 July 20; 2113 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2114, 1994 July 25; 2114 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2115, 1994 July 25; 2115 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2116, 1994 July 30; 2116 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2117, 1994 July 30; 2117 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2118, 1994 July 30; 2118 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2119, 1994 Aug. 9; 2119 (Item 43)
    "Boulder, CO; Skowhegan, ME"
  - Contact sheet 2120, 1994 Aug. 13; 2120 (Item 43)
  - Contact sheet 2121, 1994 Aug. 18; 2121 (Item 44)
    "Woodstock, NY; Henry Geldzahler's funeral"
  - Contact sheet 2122, 1994 Aug. 18; 2122 (Item 44)
    "Long Island, NY; Henry Geldzahler's funeral"
  - Contact sheet 2123, 1994 Aug. 18; 2123 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2124, 1994 Aug. 18; 2124 (Item 44)
    "Southhampton, Long Island, NY; Henry Geldzahler's funeral"
  - Contact sheet 2125, 1994 Aug. 18; 2125 (Item 44)
    "Southhampton, Long Island, NY"
  - Contact sheet 2126, 1994 Aug. 18; 2126 (Item 44)
    Roy Lichtenstein
  - Contact sheet 2127, 1994 Aug. 22; 2127 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2128, 1994 Aug. 31; 2128 (Item 44)
    "Ypsilanti, MI; New York City; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2129, 1994 Sept. 8; 2129 (Item 44)
    "Ypsilanti, MI; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 2130, 1994 Sept. 8; 2130 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2131, 1994 Sept. 10; 2131 (Item 44)
    "Ypsilanti, MI; New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ"
  - Contact sheet 2132, 1994 Sept. 11; 2132 (Item 44)
    "Los Angeles, San Francisco, NY"
  - Contact sheet 2133, 1994 Sept. 15; 2133 (Item 44)
    "Washington, DC; New York City; Jonas Mekas at National Gallery; Allen Ginsberg self portrait at optometrist"
  - Contact sheet 2134, 1994 Sept. 21; 2134 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2135, 1994 Sept. 27; 2135 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2136, 1994 Sept. 28; 2136 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; kitchen window views; Sid Kaplan at National Gallery"
    Sid Kaplan; Robert Frank
  - Contact sheet 2137, 1994 Sept. 29; 2137 (Item 44)
    "Washington, DC; New York City; skyscrapers; street scenes; homeless"
    Dave Breithaupt; Robert Frank
  - Contact sheet 2138, 1994 Oct. 1; 2138 (Item 44)
    "New York City; skyscrapers, skylines; street scenes; homeless"
    Gaidemak; Ben Schaffer
  - Contact sheet 2139, 1994 Oct. 3; 2139 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2140, 1994 Oct. 7; 2140 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; Robert Frank opening at National Gallery; Amiri Baraka birthday"
  - Contact sheet 2141, 1994 Oct. 10; 2141 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ; kitchen window views; Amiri Baraka birthday party"
  - Contact sheet 2142, 1994 Oct. 16; 2142 (Item 44)
    "Chesapeake Bay, MD; Washington, DC; Lucien Carr on boat; The Sand Piper in Chesapeake Bay"
  - Contact sheet 2143, 1994 Oct. 19; 2143 (Item 44)
    "Chesapeake Bay, MD; Washington, DC; Lucien Carr on boat; The Sand Piper in Chesapeake Bay; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes; Appeals Court PCC Press Conference"
  - Contact sheet 2144, 1994 Oct. 23; 2144 (Item 44)
    New York; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; kitchen window views; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 2145, 1994 Oct. 30; 2145 (Item 44)
    New York; kitchen window views; homeless; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 2146, 1994 Nov. 5; 2146 (Item 44)
    "Hot Springs, AR; Arlington Hotel; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2147, 1994 Nov. 11; 2147 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2148, 1994 Nov. 13; 2148 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Ann Arbor, MI; kitchen window views; "
  - Contact sheet 2149, 1994 Nov. 25; 2149 (Item 44)
    Robert Frank
  - Contact sheet 2150, 1994 Nov. 27; 2150 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2151, 1994 Dec. 1; 2151 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2152, 1994 Dec. 1; 2152 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2153, 1994 Dec. 3; 2153 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2154, 1994 Dec. 6; 2154 (Item 44)
    "London, England; Welsh Arts Festival; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Camden Road Hotel"
  - Contact sheet 2155, 1994 Dec. 13; 2155 (Item 44)
    "London, England; Paris, France; George Whitman at Shakespeare and Co.; Eiffel Tower"
  - Contact sheet 2156, 1994 Dec. 13; 2156 (Item 44)
  - Contact sheet 2157, 1994 Dec. 19; 2157 (Item 44)
    "Santa Monica, CA; New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2158, 1994 Dec. 22; 2158 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Paris, France; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2159, 1994 Dec. 27; 2159 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Paris, France; Camp Copneconic; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2160, 1995 Jan. 3; 2160 (Item 44)
    "New York City; Paris, France"
  - Contact sheet 2163, 1995 Jan. 15; 2163 (Item 45)
    "Ann Arbor, MI; New York City; subway views"
  - Contact sheet 2164, 1995 Jan. 28; 2164 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2165, 1995 Jan. 28; 2165 (Item 45)
    George Condo
  - Contact sheet 2166, 1995 Jan. 28; 2166 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2167, 1995 Feb. 2; 2167 (Item 45)
    Lita Hornick
  - Contact sheet 2168, 1995 Feb. 3; 2168 (Item 45)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians window
  - Contact sheet 2169, 1995 Feb. 3; 2169 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2170, 1995 Feb. 4; 2170 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2171, 1995 Feb. 4; 2171 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2172, 1995 Feb. 5; 2172 (Item 45)
    Francis Ford Coppola; Eric Dro
  - Contact sheet 2173, 1995 Feb. 12; 2173 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2174, 1995 Feb. 16; 2174 (Item 45)
    "San Francisco, CA; Ann Arbor, MI"
  - Contact sheet 2175, 1995 Feb. 17; 2175 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2176, 1995 Feb. 21; 2176 (Item 45)
    "Ann Arbor, MI; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 2177, 1995 Feb. 21; 2177 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2178, 1995 Feb. 22; 2178 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2179, 1995 Feb. 25; 2179 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2180, 1995 Feb. 27; 2180 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2181, 1995 Feb. 27; 2181 (Item 45)
    New York City; Natalie Merchant rehearsal
  - Contact sheet 2182, 1995 Feb. 28; 2182 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2183, 1995 Mar. 1; 2183 (Item 45)
    New York City; kitchen window views; subway posters
  - Contact sheet 2184, 1995 Mar. 6; 2184 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2185, 1995 Mar. 7; 2185 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2186, 1995 Mar. 12; 2186 (Item 45)
    New York City; Kettle of Fish; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 2187, 1995 Mar. 13; 2187 (Item 45)
    New York City; Gregory Corso in the Kettle of Fish
  - Contact sheet 2188, 1995 Mar. 13; 2188 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2189, 1995 Mar. 16; 2189 (Item 45)
    New York City; Sushed Kogan reading recession Howl Trial; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 2190, 1995 Mar. 18; 2190 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2191, 1995 Mar. 21; 2191 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2192, 1995 Mar. 21; 2192 (Item 45)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Gelek Rinpoche with Uncle Sam hat
  - Contact sheet 2193, 1995 Mar. 31; 2193 (Item 45)
  - Contact sheet 2194, 1995 Apr. 1; 2194 (Item 45)
    "Galway, Ireland"
  - Contact sheet 2195, 1995 Apr. 1; 2195 (Item 45)
    "Galway, Ireland; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2196, 1995 Apr. 1; 2196 (Item 45)
    "Galway, Ireland; kitchen window views; Sotheby's"
  - Contact sheet 2198, 1995 Apr. 2; 2198 (Item 45)
    "Galway, Ireland; Strand; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2199, 1995 Apr. 4; 2199 (Item 45)
    "Galway, Ireland; New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Circus"
  - Contact sheet 2200, 1995 Apr. 8; 2200 (Item 45)
    "Laugharne, Aberstwyth, Wales"
  - Contact sheet 2201, 1995 Apr. 12; 2201 (Item 46)
    "Laugharne, Wales; New York City; Dylan Thomas' grave; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2202, 1995 Apr. 12; 2202 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Allen Ginsberg after PEN dinner, formal wear"
  - Contact sheet 2204, 1995 Apr. 16; 2204 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2205, 1995 Apr. 18; 2205 (Item 46)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg in formal wear after PEN dinner; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; pharmacist
  - Contact sheet 2206, 1995 Apr. 19; 2206 (Item 46)
    New York City; Bob Rosenthal and Bill Morgan looking at Ed Marshall's manuscripts
  - Contact sheet 2207, 1995 Apr. 22; 2207 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Delhi, NY; Mary Help of Christians Church window"
  - Contact sheet 2208, 1995 Apr. 27; 2208 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Delhi, NY; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2209, 1995 Apr. 29; 2209 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2210, 1995 May 4; 2210 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2211, 1995 May 5; 2211 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2212, 1995 May 9; 2212 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2213, 1995 May 14; 2213 (Item 46)
    "New York City; street scenes, film crew; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2214, 1995 May 16; 2214 (Item 46)
    Daniel Ellsberg
  - Contact sheet 2215, 1995 May 20; 2215 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2216, 1995 May 21; 2216 (Item 46)
    "Halifax, Canada; Allen Ginsberg in stocks"
  - Contact sheet 2217, 1995 May 28; 2217 (Item 46)
    New York City; street scenes; kitchen window views; Larry Rivers signing condo closing papers
  - Contact sheet 2218, 1995 June 3; 2218 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Peter Orlovsky at Paterson falls; street scenes; Union Square farmers' market; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2219, 1995 June 8; 2219 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Venice, Italy; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2220, 1995 June 8; 2220 (Item 46)
    "New York City; Venice, Italy; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2221, 1995 June 9; 2221 (Item 46)
    "Venice, Italy; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2222, 1995 June 10; 2222 (Item 46)
    "Venice, Italy; St. Mark's Square"
  - Contact sheet 2223, 1995 June 12; 2223 (Item 46)
    "Venice, Amalfi, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 2224, 1995 June 15; 2224 (Item 46)
    "Amalfi, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 2225, 1995 June 15; 2225 (Item 46)
    "Amalfi, Italy; village scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2226, 1995 June 16; 2226 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2227, 1995 June 17; 2227 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2228, 1995 June 19; 2228 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2229, 1995 June 21; 2229 (Item 46)
  - Contact sheet 2230, 1995 June 21; 2230 (Item 46)
    "Amalfi, Italy; village scenes; hanging painting show; Chewancean"
  - Contact sheet 2231, 1995 June 23; 2231 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2232, 1995 June 23; 2232 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2233, 1995 June 24; 2233 (Item 47)
    "Chateau Denoiza, France; village scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2234, 1995 June 26; 2234 (Item 47)
    "Amalfi, Milan, Italy; village scenes"
  - Contact sheet 2235, 1995 June 28; 2235 (Item 47)
    "Amalfi, Milan, Italy; New York City; highway scenes; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2236, 1995 June 30; 2236 (Item 47)
    "Milan, Italy; New York City; kitchen window views; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 2237, 1995 July 4; 2237 (Item 47)
    "New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ; Boulder, CO; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 2238, 1995 July 6; 2238 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2239, 1995 July 7; 2239 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2240, 1995 July 7; 2240 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2241, 1995 July 10; 2241 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2242, 1995 July 14; 2242 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2243, 1995 July 15; 2243 (Item 47)
    "Boulder, CO; Naropa Symposium with Robin Blaser; Allen Ginsberg by Alan Brooks"
  - Contact sheet 2244, 1995 July 16; 2244 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2245, 1995 July 17; 2245 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2246, 1995 July 18; 2246 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2247, 1995 July 18; 2247 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; Lake Lone Star"
  - Contact sheet 2248, 1995 July 18; 2248 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; rowing on Lake Lone Star"
  - Contact sheet 2249, 1995 July 18; 2249 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2250, 1995 July 19; 2250 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2251, 1995 July 19; 2251 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2252, 1995 July 20; 2252 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; William Burroughs at Nelson's Diner"
  - Contact sheet 2253, 1995 July 21; 2253 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; William Burroughs shooting; shocking"
  - Contact sheet 2254, 1995 July 21; 2254 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2255, 1995 July 22; 2255 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2256, 1995 July 22; 2256 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; William Burroughs sleeping at table, Saturday supper"
  - Contact sheet 2257, 1995 July 23; 2257 (Item 47)
  - Contact sheet 2258, 1995 July 23; 2258 (Item 47)
    "Lawrence, KS; "
  - Contact sheet 2259, 1995 July 24; 2259 (Item 47)
    New York City; Mary Help of Christians Church window; city views
  - Contact sheet 2260, 1995 July 29; 2260 (Item 47)
    New York City; Kansas City landscape; pawnshop
  - Contact sheet 2261, 1995 July 29; 2261 (Item 48)
  - Contact sheet 2262, 1995 July 29; 2262 (Item 48)
    New York City; Sonic Youth on stage; Lollapalooza concert Randall's Island stadium
    Beck Hansen; Sonic Youth
  - Contact sheet 2263, 1995 July 29; 2263 (Item 48)